Hello everyone, my name is Ignacio Guarner
Sala and i am recording this video in representation
of MedConect, I am a co-author of this
web page alognside Aldrin Guzman Figueroa and we
want to share our web page. This
page is a medical encyclopedia as we will
see
later. It is still unfinished but
already have something of value to show. First,
this is our index page, where we
have a header. Here we
have a link to the University of
Alicante, here is for returning to the index,
a browser that we will see later and
other methods which we will also see
later. This is the index, here
the most important part is the
medical encyclopedia, where the articles are
organized alphabetically and the featured
articles section, which shows articles
that may be of interest. Lets enter for
example in the C section, and in the C page
we can enter in
Coronavirus. Here we have a
table of contents, all the articles
have one. Here we have tje article itself,
a video and an interactive
map. I'm not going to use it right now
because all of the links are broken, but
you can click in the different
parts and it redirects to the different
countries. Let's return to
index and let's see the browser. It
is very simple, first tou select the
category, the thing that you want
to search, if you want it to be
searched ad an "and", an "or" or
a "not" and finally you check this to
confirm the search. The browser
doesn't work right now, it send you to
Search not found, but we will make
it work. Let's go see Other methods, and
here we have a small page about the
human esqueleton, another interactive
map, this one dows work and it sends you to
the Wikipedia article about the specific bone you
choose and a table with all of the bones of the
human esqueleton. Let's return to the
index. We have the featured articles section,
and let's see the page to sends us
a message to cantact
us.
You send a subject, your role,
the date of
birth, your sex, your email addres and
you check if you want to recieve more information.
As you can see the subject and message sections
have an asterisk. This is you signal that these
are compulsory sections. If you try to send
a message without writing anything here it
laerts you with an error.
We also have a small quiz
wich is similar to the former
page.
You select your birth date, your age, a
small cognicity
test, your favourite color and your grade
of satisfaction. Again we have
compulsory
sections. We also have our accesibility
page, were we have our declaration of
accesibility,
some examples of accesibility in
documents, what is accesibility and that
we basically have a compromise to
make our web page as
accesible as
possible. FInally we have
a table of contents for our whole
web page, which has all the relevant sections and links.
YOu can access the index, articles with
a, articles with c, other methods, our
forms and the accesibility page. This
ia all and thank you for watching.